571-232-9287 (cell)

mceraolo@gmail.com

SUMMARY AND SKILLS

Mark possesses a 13-year technical background specializing in Service Desk functions with responsibilities ranging from developing custom SQL scripts, programming a COTS application, creating, maintaining, and reviewing Change and Configuration Management documentation. Mark has experience in the following domains:

- SQL
- webMethods
- PowerBuilder
- Sybase ASE
- SPS PD²
- Python

- .Net (VB and C#)
- MS Office suite
- HTML/CSS/Javascript/Bootstrap
- Oracle CRM
- ServiceNow
- XML

CERTIFICATIONS: COMPTIA SECURITY+ CE

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2017 – PRESENT SYSTEM ANALYST 3, CACI, INC.

Responsibilities are to provide functional and technical support for active DOD sites; provide customer with interim resolutions for software defects and data related errors; provide support for Sybase, Procurement Desktop-Defense (PD2), The PD2 Adapter and Federal Procurement Data Systems software; acting as the main point of contact and Subject Matter Expert (SME) on the Standard Procurement System Help Desk for all technical and functional SoftwareAG/PD² Adapter/ SPS Legacy Integrations related issues. Takes responsibility for customer issues by actively taking on new issues and following up with existing issues. Performs the following for each issue: 1) Provides accurate resolutions to customer issues. 2) Assesses the severity of the issue to ensure the customer's expectations for the issue are met. 3) Responds to issues in a timely manner and provide customers with an ongoing status of progress for their issues. Supports additional projects as requested by management such as reviewing product documentation and supporting product development testing efforts. Contributes to the overall Customer Support Knowledge Base by creating Frequently Asked Questions, training and mentoring new team members, or working with other team members to provide assistance as needed. Provides technical assistance with any/all of the following: PD2, PD2Adapter, PDS, webMethods, Sybase, PowerBuilder and SQL, to aid other Tech Support members in the Service Request resolution

MAY 2016 - APRIL 2017

i

SYSTEM ANALYST 3, CACI, INC.

Responsibilities are to provide functional and technical support for an SAP/ERP environment; provide customer with interim resolutions for software defects and data related errors; provide support for WBSCM; acting as the main point of contact and Subject Matter Expert (SME) on the WBSCM Service Desk for technical and functional related issues. Takes responsibility for customer issues by actively taking on new issues and following up with existing issues. Performs the following for each issue: 1) Provides accurate resolutions to customer issues. 2) Assesses the severity of the issue to ensure the customer's expectations for the issue are met. 3) Responds to issues in a timely manner and provide customers with an ongoing status of progress for their issues. Supports additional projects as requested by management such as reviewing product documentation and supporting product development testing efforts

AUGUST 2007 - MAY 2016 SYSTEM ANALYST 3, CACI, INC.

Responsibilities are to provide functional and technical support for active DOD sites; provide customer with interim resolutions for software defects and data related errors; provide support for PD², The PD² Adapter and Federal Procurement Data Systems software; acting as the main point of contact and Subject Matter Expert (SME) on the SPS Help Desk for all technical and functional SoftwareAG/PD² Adapter/ SPS Legacy Integrations (SPS-LI) related issues. Takes responsibility for customer issues by actively taking on new issues and following up with existing issues. Performs the following for each issue: 1) Provides accurate resolutions to customer issues. 2) Assesses the severity of the issue to ensure the customer's expectations for the issue are met. 3) Responds to issues in a timely manner and provide customers with an ongoing status of progress for their issues.

Supports additional projects as requested by management such as reviewing product documentation and supporting product development testing efforts. Contributes to the overall Customer Support knowledge base by creating Frequently Asked Questions, training and mentoring new team members, or working with other team members to provide assistance as needed. Provides technical assistance with any/all of the following: PD², PD²Adapter, PDS, webMethods, Sybase, PowerBuilder and SQL, to aid other Tech Support members in the Service Request resolution. Lead for the development and maintenance of the COTS Script-Aid utility tool application using Powerbuilder 12.5 and 12.6.

NOVEMBER 2006 - JULY 2007

CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST, LUCAS SYSTEMS INC.

Troubleshot, researched, diagnosed, documented, and resolved technical issues surrounding the Lucas Voice-Automates software products using Visual Basic. Worked with product development and project teams to track and resolve problems. Participated in and sometimes led the installation of systems at customer sites as well customer training.

OCTOBER 2005 - NOVEMBER 2006

HELP DESK SPECIALIST 2 - TECH SUPPORT, CACI, INC.

Technical troubleshooting and mitigation of software-related issues with the SPS software suite. Formulated resolutions by researching previous similar issues and reference guides. Developed diagnostic and manipulative scripts using SQL to resolve customer issues.

EDUCATION

MAY 2003
COMPUTER SCIENCE, YOUNGSTOWN STATE UNIVERSITY